[{"answer": "Why did you tell them my book was being published", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, I didn't. What I said was that my agent had heard there was some interest at Conundrum..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, then put him at the singles table", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Then put him with the that place. Whatever you and your Mom decide is fine with me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Don't dismiss me. I'm trying to include you in this decision. He's your friend", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " I'm not going to call every five minutes, but this is important", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "We're not getting any younger, right? And my career, well, it's gotten pretty, you know, frustrating. Even with my new manager. Maybe it's time to settle down", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " It does. Feels right", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " It does. Feels right", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Yeah. It's good. Feels good", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah. That's Maya", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Sure I know my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You know her", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You know that chick", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That's hilarious. You sound just like one of those guys", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You are not", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I just wanted you to know I've decided not to go to the wedding, so in case you were dreading some uncomfortable, you know, ru", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I suppose I got really into wine originally through my e", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Like what a fraud he was", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Highliner", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Bottle", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What do you think's going on", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Been checking your messages", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What's happening", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What exactly are we going to do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hey, don't pull away till they see the car", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " You were wearing your belt", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Well, let's go have some champagne, shall we? Toast all the newlyweds", "docId": "Sideways.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You quit drinking", "qsentId": 30}]